<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Workflow</title>
      <link>/posts/data-science-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/data-science-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Why it matters When working with recurring clients and projects together with tight deadlines it is easy to cut corners or forget good practice.
Here are the top reasons why a data science workflow is vital:
 Work is well documented
 Folders and files logically are structured
 Projects remain version controlled
 Data output is tracked
 Logical seperation of scripts make productizing easy
 Good naming conventions make tracking of the project flow easy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design and Analysis of Experiments with R</title>
      <link>/posts/design_and_analysis_of_experiments_with_r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/design_and_analysis_of_experiments_with_r/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This document will cover in depth the use of DoE experiments in R! We will focus our attention to measuring treatment effects, not variances.
Based on the work:
Lawson, John. Design and Analysis of Experiments with R. Chapman and Hall/CRC, 20141217. VitalBook file.
  Definitions  Experiment (also called a Run) is an action where the experimenter changes at least one of the variables being studied and then observes the effect of his or her actions(s).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Soft Introduction to Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/posts/intro-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/intro-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Important machine learning libraries Future additions  Part 1 - Data Preprocessing Part 2 - Regression Simple Linear Regression Multiple linear regression Polynomial Regression Support vector machine regression Regression Trees Random forest regression A more robust application of machine learning regressions (random forest)  Part 3 - Clustering K-means  Part 4 - Dimensionality Reduction Create PCA  Part 5 - Reinforced Learning Multi-Armed Bandit Problem Upper Confidence Bound (UCB) method Improve results using UCB Visualize the model add selection  Part 6 - Parameter Grid Search, Cross-validation and Boosting Grid Search and Parameter Tuning XGBoost    Important machine learning libraries I created this document to serve as an easy introduction to basic machine learning methods.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>